# **Pantelis Kassotis**

#### **Details**

Agios Stefanos, Attika, Greece (+30) 6985033632 info@panteliskassotis.com

#### Links

Official Website

LinkedIn Profile

GitHub Profile

Behance Profile

#### Skills

C#

C++

Python

**JavaScript** 

HTML/CSS

Interpersonal Communication

Teamwork & Positive Attitude

### Accreditations

Steamworks Developer, Feb 2021, Partner ID 130341

Unity Certified Developer, Apr 2018, Credential ID 2018034406

#### **Honors & Awards**

- Steam Community Leader, 2021, Valve Corporation
- Steam Awards Nomination Committee, 2020, Valve Corporation
- Arctic Code Vault Contributor,
  2020, Arctic World Archive
- IPMAs Best Affiliate Network Award for Rakuten Marketing,
- Best Performance Marketing Campaign, APAC for Rakuten Marketing,
- Best Retail Campaign for Rakuten Marketing,
- Best Team in Performance
  Marketing for Rakuten
  Marketing, 2019, International
  Performance Marketing Awards

# **Software Engineer / Machine Learning Specialist**

Got full stack experience creating and managing websites, apps and GUIs from the concept stage all the way to publishing. Love learning new things and tools every day. If I do not know something I will learn it.

# **Work Experience**

### Technical Infrastructure - Vedra, Valve Corporation

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

- Created a universal video game microtransaction cryptocurrency for Steam Developers.
- Reduced the time requirements between each transaction to make the coin more video game friendly by modifying the Scrypt algorithm.
- Created both ethereum and blackcoin-based servers and wallets for Windows, Apple and Linux so I can incentivize game developers to modify Vedra however they see fit and figure out better solutions for their specific needs.

Credentials: Vedra, Wallet, Vedra On Steam

### Hardware Engineering - Steam VR, Valve Corporation

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

- Making high-end gaming more approachable to the masses by helping develop the most affordable VR headset in the market that supports Steam VR.
- Improved room-scaling AI and by extent the device's precision and freedom of movement.
- Helped design a motherboard with a total production cost of \$25.
- Reduced hardware costs by 3D printing most of the parts.

Credentials: Relativity, GitHub Page, Admin Certification

## Software Engineering Consultant, Rakuten Advertising

MARCH 2018 - DECEMBER 2020

- Created award-winning apps and websites for 4 different Rakuten divisions plus Walmart.
- Helped American retailers like Target and Walmart establish a presence for millennials and Generation Z members in the difficult-to-enter Asian markets.
- Won 4 International Performance Marketing Awards (IPMAs) for "Best Affiliate Network", "Best Performance Marketing Campaign", "Best Retail Campaign" and "Best Team in Performance Marketing".

Credentials: Main Website, Target Website, Walmart Website

## **Education**

## MicroBachelors (MB), Computer Science Fundamentals, NYU Tandon School of Engineering

MAY 2020 - MARCH 2021

Activities and Societies: IBM Quantum Experience

Advanced Professional Certifications (APCs), Computer Science for Web Programming, Mobile Apps, Game Development, Artificial Intelligence, Harvard John A. Paulson School of Engineering and Applied Sciences

JANUARY 2020 - MAY 2020

Activities and Societies: CS50 (Harvard's largest course.)